Sociology 10 Course Project on Student Family Histories Collection, 1987 UA.90.08.35-T1987
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Sociology 10 Course Project on Student Family Histories Collection
1987
ULS Archives & Special Collections
University of Pittsburgh. Department of Sociology
Holzner, Burkart
UA.90.08.35-T1987
0.45 Linear Feet (1 box)
A collection of 44 student papers written for Professor Burkart Holzner's Sociolgy 10 course at the University of Pittsburgh on the sociological perspective of the author's family.
Previous Citation
Sociology 10 Course Projects on Student Family Histories Collection, UA.90.08.35-T1987, University Archives, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
The papers contained in this collection were previously included in the Archives of Industrial Societies Assorted Manuscript Collection.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions to access but photocopying or any other method of making a reproduction of the contents is not allowed.
Scope and Content Notes
Students in Professor Burkart Holzer's Sociology 10 course at the University of Pittsburgh were assigned a class project to write about their family history to demonstrate their understanding of sociological terms and concepts. This collection contains 44 student papers from that course. Students were ask to sign a waiver so that their papers could be given to the Archives Service Center for its Pennsylvania Ethnic Studies program.
University of Pittsburgh; Family histories -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Family histories; Term papers; Sociology -- Study and teaching (Higher) -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Ethnic groups
- Project description and waiver form, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Amoroso, Dina,"Social Changes in the Family", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Bartasavich, Francine,"Sociological Changes in Three Generations of my Family History", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Blank, Linda M., 1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Camp, Lisa,"A Look at Changes Brought on By the Post World War II Population Explosion", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Cardone, J.,"From Italians to Americans", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Ceravelo, Jill, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Donald, Douglas,"Social Change", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Ferretti, Toni A., 1987 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Giglio, Christine,"Sociology Paper", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Henninger, David L.,"The Henninger's", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Hillsman, Andria, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Housch, Robin,"An Analysis of Social Change in My Family", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Jasuta, Lisa, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Johnson, Dana,"Sociology Paper", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Lammey, Robert,"Sociology 010 Class Project", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Koeppl, Dan,"Sociology Paper", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Lutz, Cathy,"Sociology Project", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Margolis, Lynn,"Social Change Among Family History", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- McCarthy, Sharon,"Class Project", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- McLaughlin, Kerry,"Sociology in the Steel Industry", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Mills, Scott A.,"The Political Activity and Awareness Theory", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Moore, Sandra,"Differences Between the Ages", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Peterson, Sherri,"Sociology 10 Class Project", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Rapp, Karen, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Ragsdak, T.,"The Transitional Effect Between Two Generations", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Renk, Brian, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Robinson, Scott, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Rugh, Lori,"The Rugh Family From Then to Now", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Salzmann, Laura E., 1987 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- DeLuca, Jim, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Schwartz, Lisa,"Analysis of Social Changes in My Family", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Sherman, Meredith, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Skalniak, David B., 1987 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Smith, Anthony C.,"Sociology Class Project", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Smith, Randy, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Starta, Mary Ann, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Toor-Sandhu, Bina, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Triglia, Laura, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Valley, Pamela,"Three Generations of Change as Seen in the Women of My Family", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Wyse, Danelle,"Social Change", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Wignovich, Christopher, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Wilbert, Frank,"Sociological Changes Within Family Generation", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Wolf, Lloyd III, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Zeszutek, Bernie, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 45)